This is perfect. We've now got a successful deploy dot j s script
简直完美，现在我们有了一个成功的 "deploy.js" 脚本
that can deploy, verify, and then interact with our code. This is fantastic.
它可以部署，验证并与我们的代码进行交互，真是太棒了
This hard hat thing seems pretty cool. What else can we do with hard hat
Hardhat 真是太酷了，它还能做哪些事呢？
like I showed you before.
就像我之前向你们展示的
Hard Hat comes with these tasks.
Hardhat 自带的 task 有这些
And the number of tasks that Hardhead can come with can be extended by us writing plugins,
并且 Hardhat 可执行的 task 数可以通过我们编写的插件进行扩展
we can actually write our own tasks in hardhat.
我们实际上可以在 Hardhat 中编写我们自己的 task
And in our Hardhead dot config, it can defaulted with this task account,
在我们的 "hardhat.config" 中，默认有一个 task 是 "accounts"
we can see task accounts, prints the list of accounts,
可以看到 "task("accounts", "Prints the list of accounts")"
and just prints a list of accounts here
功能就是打印 accounts 的列表
actually go to the heart had documentation to learn more about creating our own tasks,
实际上，我们可以前往 Hardhat 的文档学习更多有关创建自己 task 的内容
one of the ways that you can define tasks is directly in our heart head.config.js.
其中一种定义 task 的方式就是直接在我们的 "hardhat.config.js" 中定义
But typically, what people do
但通常，人们采取的做法更多是
is they have a new folder called tasks where they put all their tasks.
创建一个名为 "tasks" 的新文件夹，将所有 task 放在这里面
So for now, I'm gonna go ahead and delete this section here.
所以现在，我会把这部分内容删掉
And we're going to create our own task.
并创建一个属于我们自己的 task
You'll notice that now that we've deleted that section,
你会发现，现在我们删掉了这部分
if we run yarn RDAP, we no longer see the accounts task in here,
如果我们运行 "yarn hardhat"，就不会在这里再看到 "accounts" task 了
because we've just deleted that task.
因为我们刚刚删除了那个 task
So let's create our own new task. We'll call this block number.js.
让我们开始创建属于我们自己的新 task，把它命名为 "block-number.js"
And we'll use this to get the current block number or whatever blockchain that we're working with.
我们会用它来获取当前的区块编号，无论我们是在使用哪个区块链
So let's create this task.
让我们来创建这个 task
First, we need to import the task function,
首先，我们需要导入 "task" 函数
we can get it by saying const task equals require arhat slash config.
可以这样做 "const  = require("hardhat/config")"
The hard hat slash config has the task function.
"hardhat/config" 中有这个 "task" 函数
To define a task, we can now just say task, give it a name and a description,
要定义一个 task ，可以这样做 "task()"，并给它一个名称和描述
the name is going to be blocked number.
名称就是 "block-number"
And then the description is going to be prints the current block number.
而描述就是 "Prints the current block number"
Now that we have this task,
现在我们有了这个 task，
there's a couple of things we can actually do with it,
就可以来做这么几件事
we can add different parameters to it by using the dot add command,
我们可以使用 ".add" 命令来向它添加不同的参数
which allow us to pass parameters to the task.
它允许我们可以向 task 传递参数
And then we could also set actions which define what the task should actually do
接着我们还可以设置 "setAction"，它定义了这个 task 实际应该执行什么
for us, we're just going to do dot set action.
对我们来说，要做的就是 ".setAction"
And define what we want this function to do.
并定义我们想让这个函数做的事
So we're going to make this an async function,
我们要创建一个 "async" 函数
that's going to take as an input, the task arguments, which are going to be blank for us,
它的输入是 "taskArgs"，对我们来说是空白的
and the HR E, which I'll define in a second.
还有 "hre"，接下来就定义它
Now, let me explain the syntax really quickly. This might look a little bit weird,
现在我来快速解释一下这些语法，这些东西看起来可能有些怪
but this is what's known as a JavaScript arrow function.
但这就是所谓的 JavaScript 箭头函数
In JavaScript, you can actually define functions without even using the function keyword.
在 JavaScript 中，定义一个函数甚至可以不需要使用 "function" 关键字
For example, if we go back to our deploy function,
比如说，如果我们回到 "deploy"
we have our async function verify down here.
这里有一个叫 "verify" 的异步函数
However, another way we could have defined this is
然而，有另一种定义方式是
is without using the function word at all,
完全不使用 "function" 关键字
and actually turning this whole thing into a variable,
这下这堆东西就变成了一个变量
we could have said instead, we could say const verify is going to be an async function
取而代之的是，我们可以 "const verify" 它是一个 "async" 函数
that takes contract addresses and arguments.
获取 "contractAddress" 还有 "args"
And here's the function definition.
以及，这里就是函数定义的内容
These two lines are essentially equivalent.
这两行本质上是等价的
There's some slight differences between between using the function keyword and having your function be a variable.
只有一点微小的区别就是，使用 "function" 关键字或是把函数变成一个变量
But for the purposes of this course, they're basically the same.
但在本课程中，它们基本上就是相同的
Which means though, that this by itself is a function,
这意味着，这个语句本身就是一个函数
just not assigned to a variable.
只是没有被分配给某个变量
But essentially, the two of these do are exactly the same.
但本质上讲，这二者就是完全相同的
And that's the syntax that we're doing here.
这就是我们在这里所使用的语法
You can imagine this sort of being like const block task equals async function,
你可以想象这个就是 "const blockTask = async function()"
which takes the params and then runs that arrow function.
获取一些参数，然后运行箭头函数
Or you can think of it as async. Function, block task parameters, and then the function definition,
或是你可以把它想成 "async function blockTask" 输入参数，然后是函数定义
these are all essentially the same.
本质上来说它们是相同的
The major difference is that we're never giving our function a name,
主要区别就是，我们没有给我们的函数命名
we never give it this block task variable.
也没有把它赋给一个叫做 "blockTask" 的变量
This is known as an anonymous function in JavaScript, because it doesn't have a name.
这就是 JavaScript 中的匿名函数("anonymous function")，因为它没有名称
Now that we have our function in here,
现在我们有了这个函数
we can now call some function to get the block number.
就可以调用某些函数来获取区块编号了
Well, how can we get the block number
那么我们该如何获取区块编号呢？
when we run tasks, we automatically pass our anonymous functions, the task arguments,
每当我们运行 task 时，都会自动向匿名函数传入 "taskArgs"
which in this one, we don't have any,
但在这个 task 中，并没有什么参数
but we also pass this HR II object. This HRV is the heart hat runtime environment.
同时我们还传入了一个 "hre" 对象，这个 "hre" 就是 "HardhatRuntimeEnvironment"(Hardhat 运行环境)
Back in our deploy script, this is basically the same as this require hard hat in here.
回到我们的 "deploy" 脚本，它基本就相当于这里的 "require("hardhat")"
So this HRV can access a lot of the same,
所以所以这个 "hre" 可以访问许多...
this HRV can access a lot of the same packages that the hard hat package can.
这个 "hre" 可以访问许多 hardhat 可以访问的包
So we can do Hae dot ethers, just like how you can import ethers from hard hat.
所以我们可以这样做 "hre.ethers"，就像你可以从 "hardhat" 中导入 "ethers" 一样
And in our ethers package, there's actually a number of functions we can use
在 "ethers" 包中就有许多函数可以用了
like dot Pro, biter dot get block number.
比如 ".provider.getBlockNumber"
Let's save this to a variable
让我们把它保存成一个变量
const blocked number equals, and this is going to be a synchronous,
"const blockNumber = "，这是一个异步的
so we're going to want to add a weight here.
所以我们要在这里添加一个 "await"
And then let's do console dot log block number.
接着我们要做的是 "console.log(blockNumber)"
Or better yet, we'll string interpolate this and say current block number like this.
或者更好的是，使用字符串插值 "Current block number" 就像这样
Now though, if I try to run this task,
现在，如果我尝试运行这个 task
you'll notice it doesn't show up in the heart Atlas of tasks,
你就会发现它并没有出现在 hardhat 的 task 列表中
let's do yarn. Art app. Hmm, I don't see block number in here.
让我们运行 "yarn hardhat"，哈，这里并没有看到 "block-number"
Well, this is because we need to add it to our config
这是因为我们还需要把它添加进我们的 ".config" 文件
dot config will add require dot slash tasks slash block number.
在我们的 ".config" 中添加 "require("./tasks/block-number")"
And in order for us to import it, and let's add a module that exports
为了导入它，让我们添加一个 "module.exports"
I'll explain what this does a little bit later.
我会稍后解释一下它的用处
But now that we've required it, if I run yarn hard hat,
现在我们已经把它 "require" 进来了，如果我运行 "yarn hardhat"
and now see blocked over is one of the tasks that I can use.
现在就可以看到 "block-number" 是一个可用的 task 了
Now for a run yarn, art hat block number,
现在运行 "yarn hardhat block-number"
we get current block number is zero.
可以获得当前区块编号为 0
And this makes sense because this is defaulting to our Hard Hat Network,
这是正确的，因为我们使用的是默认的 "Hardhat Network"
which gets reset every time we run it.
它每次运行后都会重置
But if I run yarn, hard hat block number A dash dash network Rinkeby,
但如果我运行 "yarn hardhat block-number --network rinkeby "
what do you think I'm gonna get? Again, a much larger number, current block number is right here.
你觉得会获得什么？是一个很大的数字，当前区块编号就在这里
Because this is the actual block number of Rigby
因为这就是 Rinkeby 的真实区块编号
versus the block number of our heart ad network is going to be zero
而我们 "Hardhat Network" 的区块编号仍然是 0
because it gets reset every single time, we run one of these scripts
因为每次运行这些脚本时，它都会被重置
now scripts and tasks both can basically do the same thing.
现在脚本和 task 基本可以做到相同的事了
They both can interact with contracts, they both can deploy smart contracts,
它们都可以与合约交互，都可以部署智能合约
they can both pretty much do everything.
它们几乎可以做到任何事
I prefer scripts just as a general rule of thumb,
通常来说，我更喜欢使用脚本
because I don't always think adding a special thing from the command line makes sense.
因为我不想总是在命令行上添加特定的东西
So I prefer scripts, but you'll see a ton of tasks and examples out there as well.
所以我更喜欢使用脚本，但你同时也会见到许多使用 task 的示例
I think tasks are really nice for specific use cases.
我认为 task 在某些特定情形下很有用
But for the most part, we're pretty much going to use exclusively scripts,
但大多数情况下，我们几乎只会使用脚本
but it is good to know what a task looks like and how to use it.
但了解 task 是什么样并且如何使用的，仍然很有好处
I think tasks are better for plugins
我认为 task 更适合用于插件
and scripts are better for your own local development environment.
而脚本更适合用于你自己的本地开发环境
But if you want to do everything with tasks, you absolutely can.
不过如果你想用 task 来完成所有事情，当然也可以了